Contact



jafaramini.dev@gmail.com



in jafar-amini-5715b8196



Jafar Amini Angular Developer

Summary

I have over 4 years of experience as an Angular developer. Also I worked as a full-stack freelancer programmer for about 4 years before working as an employee in companies. My top skills are: Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, RestAPI, Bootstrap, Material, MongoDB and MySQL.

Experience

Angular Developer

Pardazeshgaran Behin Sayar Co

Jan 2018 – Present

As a Frontend web developer using these technologies: Angular, HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Material and etc.

Java Spring Developer

Pardazeshgaran Behin Sayar Co

Jul 2017 - Dec 2017

As a Backend developer using these technologies: Spring Boot, MongoDB and etc.

Full Stack Developer

Dadeh Kavan Tejarat Adsay Co

Aug 2015 - Sep 2016

As a full stack developer using these technologies: Spring MVC, JSP, MySQL, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap and etc.

Full Stack Developer

Freelance

Feb 2011 - Aug 2013

As a full stack developer using these technologies: PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery.



Education

- \checkmark Master's degree, Computer Software Engineering
- \checkmark Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering

Languages

- √ Azerbaijani
- √ English
- √ Persian